VICTOR WOROBEC

victorworobec@gmail.com · Sydney, New South Wales, Australia linkedin.com/in/victor-worobec · github.com/vworo

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Versatile, driven software engineer, graduated from General Assembly's Software Engineering Immersive and with one year of Game Development studies at Sydney's Academy of Interactive Entertainment. Possessing experience in collaborative team-based work, project management and problem-solving, I am now seeking professional work where I can contribute my collaborative and strong technical skills towards a common goal.

STRENGTHS AND EXPERTISE

Javascript/Typescript React/Vue Communication

C++ Ruby/Rails Adaptability HTML/CSS Firebase/MongoDB Attention-to-detail

PROJECTS

IQEQ August 2024

Group Project - Musketeer Digital

A web application made to assist primary teachers with educating students in mathematical coursework. Exercises include simple arithmetic such as addition and multiplication, as well as image representations of such exercises. Students can also view high scores.

Accomplishments:

- Collaborated with senior dev and junior dev to build client website.
- Built a user-friendly frontend, translated from Figma designs.
- Designed and utilized re-usable components for the frontend.
- Authorized users through Next-Auth and MongoDB, using bcryptjs for password hashing.
- Retrieval and display of data such as exercise questions and high scores through API endpoints.

BeatBox May 2023

Group Project - General Assembly

This project is a web application that mimics the functionality of Spotify using Spotify's OAuth system. Users can authenticate with their Spotify accounts and access features such as browsing playlists, searching for songs, and playing music (click on a song to listen).

Accomplishments:

- Co-managed a small team in developing a music player using Vite and React.
- Managed user authentication through Spotify OAuth.
- Display of user playlists and profile using access tokens.
- Retrieval of current trending playlists for display on the home page.
- Song playback using the Spotify Web Playback SDK.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Musketeer Digital Junior Software Developer

June 2024 - Current

Collaborated with a team of senior and junior developers to bring client visions to life, using Slack and Zoom meetings as communication channels, and Figma as a medium between designers and developers.

Accomplishments:

- Communicated with team to carry out designs, tasks and bug fixes for client delivery.
- Frontend development using the React and NextJS tech-stack.
- Backend development using MongoDB and MongoDB Compass.
- Resolved bug issues assigned and rectified Github commits through requested changes.
- Structured and built reusable components to be incorporated in the frontend.
- · Handled styling through Material UI

Iplex Pipelines Production Worker

March 2022 - March 2023

Supported a team of thirty split across four teams on a rotating shift basis, manufacturing and producing water, sewer, and electrical pipe products on 24/7 schedule with equipment being changed, maintained and repaired between varying products.

Accomplishments:

- Manufactured water, sewer and electrical PVC pipe to Australian standards.
- Consistently maintained less than 5% reject rate on manufactured pipe across assigned jobs.
- Accurately and efficiently maintained production, change-over and repair duties of machinery.
- Adjusted production to account for changing deadlines of clients, demonstrating agility and flexibility.
- Supported services for a large number of Sydney's major infrastructure.

EDUCATION

General Assembly

March 2023 - June 2023

Software Engineering Immersive

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

January 2017 - December 2017

Advanced Diploma in Games Programming

References are available on request.